<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Furniture Ecommerce App UI</string>
    <string name ="CookeR_Description">Normal Electric Items Need Full Electrical Energy To Work Properly. But This Cooker Need Energy Only For Heat.You Can Make Foods With The Help Of The Special Pressure System.
So You Can Make Your Foods By Using Low Energy.</string>
    <string name = "Cooker_des2">As the Suggestion Of the Complex Economical Situation, Normally You Can Use Rice Cookers, Pressure Cookers, Ovens, Frying Pans in the Kitchen and therefore You can spend Lot of Money for those things.
Now You Can use This Universal Multi-function Smart Pressure Cooker For those Different Purposes. And also you can manage the space in the Kitchen.</string>
<string name = "watalappan_recipe1">
    Preheat oven to 160°C ten minutes before baking. Greas
e the pan before baking. Take a big pan below add half
water to it.

</string>
    <string name = "watalappan_recipe_line2">Take hot boiling water and mix jaggery to it. Keep stirring
 until dissolved completely. Strain if required. Keep it as
ide.</string>
    <string name="watalappan_recipe_line3">If using fresh coconut grate and grind into the processor.
Add little water while grinding. Squeeze the milk out wit
h the help of cloth Or mesh strainer. Remember only th
e first thick coconut milk Or cream should be utilized for
 this recipe.</string>
    <string name="watalappan_recipe_line4">Beat eggs for 3 to 4 mins. Now add coconut milk.
Beat again until all mix well. Now add jaggery water mixt
ure along with rose water. Also, combine mixed spice po
wder. Mix all well with a beater or spoon.</string>
    <string name = "watalappan_recipe_line5">Finally, add cashew nuts. Pour the batter into greased
ramekins Or pan on a water bath. Bake at 160°C for
 about an hour Or until the skewer comes out almost
 clean.</string>
    <string name="watalappan_recipe_line6">Let the custard cools own for about 10 to 15 mins.
 Dust some cocoa powder on the top. Now gently
 unmould the custard on serving plate.</string>
    <string name ="watalappan_recipe_line7">
        For Frosting:
Take a pan add water and butter. Now add sugar. Keep
the heat on low mode. Constantly keep stirring. The
sugar will dissolve and change its color. After 2 mins
remove from fire. Let this slightly cool down else the
pudding might break.
    </string>
    <string name="watalappan_recipe_line8">Pour this mixture on the pudding.
Dust some cocoa powder on the custard.
 Decorate with few cashews and the chopped dry
 coconut</string>

</resources>
